"lang"
{
	"Language" "english"
	"Tokens"
	{
		"PL_prophunt"		"Prop Hunt"
		"PL_prophunt_lobby"		"Prop Hunt"
		"PL_prophunt_desc"		"Hide as a prop from the map or hunt them down. Teams swap roles every round."
		"PL_prophunt_hint"		"Props: R reroll, Q decoy, F lock, E freeze, G taunt. Hunters: find every prop, but every miss costs 10 seconds."
		"PL_prophunt_abbr"		"PH"
		"PL_prophunt_playlist_desc"		"Prop Hunt on Township, Colony, Angel City and Complex"
		"GAMEMODE_PROPHUNT"		"Prop Hunt"
		"PH_SCOREBOARD_ELIMS"		"Eliminations"
		"PL_hotpotato"		"Hot Potato"
		"PL_hotpotato_lobby"		"Hot Potato"
		"PL_hotpotato_desc"		"Melee a pilot to pass the hot potato before it explodes. Last pilot alive wins!"
		"PL_hotpotato_hint"		"Melee another pilot to pass. Passing never resets the fuse."
		"PL_hotpotato_abbr"		"HP"
		"PL_hotpotato_playlist_desc"		"Tag another pilot to pass the hot potato. Last pilot standing wins."
		"GAMEMODE_HOTPOTATO"		"Hot Potato"
		"PL_hotpotato_playlist_hint"		"Only the carrier can melee. Hack the supply pod once per round for a tactical."
		"HP_SCOREBOARD_WINS"		"Round wins"
			"GAMEMODE_BODYSWAP" "Body Swap"
			"PL_bodyswap" "Body Swap"
			"PL_bodyswap_lobby" "Body Swap Lobby"
			"PL_bodyswap_desc" "Team deathmatch where, every few seconds, everyone swaps bodies with a random enemy: their spot, their health, their loadout. Titans swap with titans."
			"PL_bodyswap_hint" "Every few seconds, everyone swaps bodies with a random enemy. Watch your step."
			"PL_bodyswap_abbr" "SWAP"
			"GAMEMODE_PARTYLOBBY" "Party Lobby"
		"PL_partylobby" "Party Lobby"
		"PL_partylobby_lobby" "Party Lobby"
		"PL_partylobby_desc" "Vote for the next game and ready up."
		"PL_partylobby_hint" "Vote at a screen, then ready up"
		"PL_partylobby_abbr" "LOBBY"
		"PL_VOTE_PROMPT" "Press %use% to vote"
		"TIP_001" "Thanks to KrwawyMietek for helping with the playtest!"
		"TIP_002" "Thanks to drachenfruchl for helping with the playtest!"
		"TIP_003" "Thanks to Patrick_RR for helping with the playtest!"
		"TIP_004" "Thanks to Skiffy for helping with the playtest!"
		"TIP_005" "Thanks to fedamark for helping with the playtest!"
		"TIP_006" "Thanks to DaiiZ/Nidorine for helping with the playtest!"
		"TIP_007" "The RE45 is Ceaika's main and favourite gun."
		"TIP_008" "Nobody ask me what happened to trying to port Fracture to Titanfall 2."
		"TIP_009" "Hopefully you have enough friends."
		"TIP_010" "Fun fact: During this project, I have not slept for approximately 29 hours."
		"TIP_011" "The party sure is packed."
		"TIP_012" "yo omg the re45 spins look!!!!!"
		"TIP_013" "Generic tip that will not help you in any way."
		"TIP_014" "Juggernaut: one player is a massive Titan, everyone else hunts it. Hack terminals for boosts and keep the damage coming to get promoted."
		"TIP_015" "Juggernaut: as the Titan, you don't need to kill everyone. Outlast the hunters until the timer runs out and you hold the crown."
		"TIP_016" "Hot Potato: whoever has the potato is on a timer. Melee another pilot to pass it before it explodes. Last pilot alive wins."
		"TIP_017" "Hot Potato: holding the potato makes you faster and lets you see everyone nearby. Use it to chase someone down."
		"TIP_018" "Prop Hunt: props, R gives you a new disguise, Q drops a decoy, F locks your rotation and E freezes you in place."
		"TIP_019" "Prop Hunt: hunters, every shot that misses takes 10 seconds off the clock. Listen for the whistles before you fire."
		"TIP_020" "Prop Hunt: hunters, shooting a decoy stuns you for a moment. Look twice before you shoot that suspicious barrel."
		"TIP_021" "Body Swap: every few seconds everyone swaps bodies with an enemy, loadout and all. Watch for the 3, 2, 1."
		"TIP_022" "Body Swap: these maps have death pits. A swap at the wrong moment can drop you right next to one."
		"TIP_023" "Body Swap: every now and then a pilot swaps with an enemy Titan. Yes, really."
		"TIP_024" "Infection: survivors against the infected. Get killed and you join the infected. Three rounds on Live Fire maps, then back to the lobby."
		"TIP_025" "Free for All: no teams, no friends, just you. First to the score limit wins."
		"TIP_026" "The Hidden: one nearly invisible player hunts everyone else. Stick together and listen."
		"TIP_027" "One in the Chamber: one bullet, one kill. Land a kill to get your bullet back, miss and it's down to your fists."
		"TIP_028" "Gun Game: every kill moves you up to the next weapon. Get a kill with the last one to win."
		"TIP_029" "Lobby: walk up to a screen to vote, then hold to ready up. Once most people are ready the countdown starts."
		"TIP_030" "Camera stuck in the floor after a respawn? Type !stuck in chat."
	}
}
